Negative
I Would Dream of You
If there were no Sun or Moon,
I could manage
If there were no water or air
If there were no verses or melodies
I could manage
But if I didn't have you
What would I do then?
If I had somewhere to go
I wouldn't leave
If I had something to say
I would stay silent
And even if I could sing for someone else
I wouldn't sing to him
Because if I didn't have you
What would I do then?
I would dream of you
I would make you out of dreams
Because if you exist
Then I exist too
If there were no Sun or Moon
I could manage
If there were no water or air
If there were no verses or melodies
I could manage
But if I didn't have you
What would I do then?
I would dream of you
I would make you out of dreams
Because if you exist
Then I exist too
I would dream of you
I would make you out of dreams
Because if you exist
Then I exist too
I would dream of you
I would make you out of dreams
Because if you exist
Then I exist too
I would, I would dream of you
I would, I would, I would dream of you
Because if you exist
Then I exist too